<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<ItemCollection>
	<Item>
		<id>0</id>
		<name>[Leader] Master Storm Caller</name>
		<dice>"D6+2 [3-8]"</dice>
		<passive>
-(Haze) Vikings can only be killed by Zombie attacks.
		</passive>
		<active>-[0 PP] (Call Thunder) Discard one card to gain 2 PP.
-[3 PP] (GG - Godsend Gust) Vikings receive Quickness(1) and Zombies receive Slowness(1), both for their next Movement Phase.

-[3 PP] (Trampling Hail) Untill the end of the next Zombie Phase, all Warp Spaces are disabled (they are treated as an Empty space).

-[5 PP] (Heavy Rain) Remove all Status Effects from all Characters

-[X + 1 PP] (Sumon Hurricane) All Spaces in Range(X) become Hurricane Zones until the start of the next Viking Phase. All Weakling Zombies that are in or enter a Hurricane Zone are instantly destroyed.
</active>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<id>1</id>
		<name>Dice Master</name>
		<dice>D6+2[3 - 8]</dice>
		<passive>
-(Mischief) Quickness effects are doubled for you.
		</passive>
		<active>
-[2 PP] (Trickster) Target Viking in Range(3) that has not moved yet this Round re-roll dice.

-[3 PP] (Roll Breaker) Target Character in Range(5) receives Threatened(X). X is your current total movement for this turn."
		</active>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<id>2</id>
		<name>Gambler</name>
		<dice>D12Min3[3 - 12]</dice>
		<passive>
-(Lucky 7) You always draw a Blessing when you land on a Random Card Space.

-(Unlucky 13) You draw 2 Curses when you land on a Curse Space.
		</passive>
		<active>
-[1 PP] (R. Roulette) Target Viking in Range(3) randomly gains 3 PP or loses 1 PP.

-[2 PP] (House Wins) Randomly draw 1 Blessing or 1 Curse.

-[10 PP] (All in) Randomly gain or lose 1 stock. If you gained the stock, also gain 5 PP.
		</active>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<id>3</id>
		<name>Earl Stone Beard Mean Face</name>
		<dice>D10Max8[1-8]</dice>
		<passive>
-(Warrior) When landing, kill Zombies in Range(1) that have Fear.
		</passive>
		<active>
-[3 PP] (The Look) Change direction to the one they came from to target Zombie in Range(5).
		  
-[X+1 PP] (Intimidate) Target Zombie in Range(X) receives Fear untill the end of the next Viking Phase (That Zombie cannot kill any Character by any means)."
		</active>
	</Item>

</ItemCollection>